A Guide to the Records of the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority [DRAFT], 1955-1973
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority [DRAFT], 1955-1973
The Library of Virginia
40941
15.65 cu. ft. (43 boxes)
Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on
Biographical Information
The Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority was established in 1955 to build the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike. The Authority was a small state agency created by the General Assembly, to administer (design, finance, acquire right-of-way, construct, operate, collect tolls, and maintain) the Turnpike. The Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike (RPT) cost $76.7 million (funded with proceeds from toll revenue bonds sold by the Commonwealth of Virginia) to build, and it ran for 34.7 miles from US-1 in Dinwiddie County to US-301 in Henrico County (from today's I-85 Exit 63 to I-95 Exit 82), it opened in its entirety on July 1, 1958; and soon after opening, the RPT was designated with the I-85 and I-95 designations, even though no federal aid was used to build the RPT, and it became part of the Interstate system. The 1973 General Assembly passed legislation to dissolve the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority and transfers its duties, powers and obligations to the Virginia State Highway Commission (the predecessor of the current Commonwealth Transportation Board), so the Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation (today's VDOT) took over administration of the RPT in 1973.
Scope and Content
Records, 1954-1973, including agreements, brochures, by-laws, correspondence, engineering reports, finances, maps, photographs, and reports of the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority. The collection is housed in two series: Series I: Papers, 1955-1973; and Series II: Photographs, 1954-1958. The bulk of the collection consists of works progress photographs. The photographs are noteable as they document the destruction of many blocks of homes and businesses in Jackson Ward, Richmond's oldest historically African-American community. The highway bisected the neighborhood and has had irreparable effects on its fabric.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into two series:
Series I: Papers, 1955-1973
Series II: Photographs, 1955-1973
Contents List
- Series I: Papers, 1955-1973., Extent: 3.4 cu. ft. (8 boxes). (Box 1-8)
  Series I: Papers, 1955-1973, are housed in eight boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series includes agreements, brochures, by-laws, correspondence, designs, finances, legislation, reports, specifications, and oversize maps. Of note are the agreements, designs, and correspondence between the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority and Parsons, Brinckerhoff, Hall & MacDonald, engineers, and Coverdale & Colpitts, consulting engineers. Included is correspondence, engineering reports, legal papers, and statements on the financing and sale of bonds to fund the building of the Turnpike. Several examples of other states bonds are included. Also included are reports on the estimated traffic and revenue of the turnpike; revised toll schedules; plan of operation; and report on holiday accident and fatalities. Of note are brochures from other state turnpikes and stickers created for the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority.
  Also included are oversize right of way plans, Colonial Heights access ramp plans, route maps, and topographical plans. Of note is a map of the route that acts as a key to the numbering of photographs in Series II: Photographs.
  - Agreement for preliminary engineering services, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - By-laws, 1954-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Heights Access ramp, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Colonial Heights Access ramp, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Heights Access ramp, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Heights Access ramp, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Contract 10, Design calculations: Bridges B-64, B-65, B-67, B-68, and B-70, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence, Commonwealth of Virginia, 1954-1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Coverdale & Colpitts, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Hunton, Williams, Gay, Moore & Powell, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Mitchell, Pershing, Shetterly & Mitchell, 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1958-1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financing, Bank loan for preliminary work, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
  - Financing, Bonds-Printing, 1955-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Financing, Bonds-Sale, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Financing, Bonds-Sale, 1955-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Financing, Estimates and schedules, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Financing, Official statements, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Financing, Additional, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Financing, Additional, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Holiday accident and fatality reports, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Interim engineering report, 1971 July (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Invitations, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - John Tyler Technical College, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Legislation, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Notes, Review comments, 1973 March (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Plan of operation, 1963 October (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Report on estimated traffic and revenues, 1955 August (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Revised toll schedule, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Stickers, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Turnpike brochures [Connecticut-New York], 1956-1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Turnpike brochures [Pennsylvania-West Virginia], 1956-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Turnpike supplemental specifications, 1956 March (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, Bureau of Public Roads, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council, Committee on bonds, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council, Committee on bonds, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Road Builder [magazine], 1968 September (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Widening and improvement program [draft], 1973 March (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
  - Oversize maps and key to photographs (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Series II: Photographs, 1956-1958., Extent: 12.25 cu. ft. (35 boxes). (Box 9-43)
  Series II: Photographs, 1956-1958, are housed in thirty-five boxes and arranged alphabetically by contract number.
  A map of the route that acts as a key to the numbering of photographs is located in Series I: Papers, Oversize maps and key to photographs (b8 f1).
  - Contract No. A-2-G, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    Wiley N. Jackson Co., contractors
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1956 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
    D.W. Winkleman Co., Inc., contractors
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1956 November 14 (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1956 December 17 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 March 13 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 June 17 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 August 14 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 September 19 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 October 14 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1957 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    Blythe Brothers Co., Inc., contractors
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1958 February 12 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1958 May 14 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-3-G, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 February 7, 10, 12 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    E.G. Bowles-Wiley N. Jackson Co., contractors
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 March 5 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 March 23 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 March 27 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 May 23 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 June 27 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 July 24 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 August 28 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 September 25 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 October 23 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 December 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957 December 30 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1958 January 22 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1958 January 28 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1958 March 3 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1958 March 28 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1958 July 22 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. A-4-G, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 April 25 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    W.E. Graham & Son's, contractors
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 May 24 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 July 15 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 August 20 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 September 16 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 November 12 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 December 12 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 January 13 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 February 12 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 March 11 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 April 8 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 May 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1958 June 10 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 April-December (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-4-S, 1957 December-1958 June (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1956 December 21 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Wiley N. Jackson Co., Robert T. Main Co., Thorington Const. Co., contractors
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 January 15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 February 11 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 March 11 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 April 15 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 May 13 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 June 17 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 July 15 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 August 12 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 September 16 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 October 14 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 November 11 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 December 16 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 January 13 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 February 24 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 March 17 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 April 14 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 May 12 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 June 16 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1958 July 14 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1956 December-1957 August (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, 1957 August-1958 July (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. A-5-G, Negatives, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. B-1-Sub, 1956 June-October (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Bowers Construction Co., contractors
  - Contract No. B-1-Sub, 1956 November 21-1957 July (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. B-2-Sub, 1956 October-1957 March (Box 21, Folder 3)
    T.A. Loving Co., contractors
  - Contract No. B-2-Sub, 1957 April-December (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1957 December 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Thorington Construction Co., contractors
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1957 December 27 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1958 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1958 May 1 and 12 and June 10 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1958 July 22 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1957 December 3-1958 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1958 March 24-April 23 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, 1958 May 1-June 10 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. B-3-Sup, Negatives, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1957 November 6 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    American Bridge Division United States Steel Corp., contractors
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1957 December 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1957 December 27 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1958 January 27 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1958 February 27 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1958 August 10 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, 1958 August 10-11 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. B-4-Str, Negatives, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 February 18 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Villa Contracting Co., Inc., contractors
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 March 21 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 April 25 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 May 24 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 June 24 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 July 24 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 August 23 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 September 23 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 September 25 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 October 21 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 November 22 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957 December 23 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1958 January 28 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1958 February 25 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1959 March 28 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1958 April 25 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1958 May 26 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. C-1-G, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 March 21 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    S.J. Groves & Son's, contractors
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 April 24 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 May 24 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 June 24 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 August 23 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 September 23 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 October 21 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 November 22 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957 December 23 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1958 January 28 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1958 February 25 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1958 March 28 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1958 April 25 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1958 May 26 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-2-G, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 April 11 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Wright Contracting Co., contractors
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 May 10 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 June 10 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 July 11 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 August 12 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 September 12 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 October 11 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 November 8 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957 December 15 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 January 18 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 February 10 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 March 12 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 April 9 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 May 9 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 June 9 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1958 July 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. C-3-G, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1956 September 17 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1956 October 18 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1956 December 5, 19 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 January 18 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 February 20 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 March 18 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 May 18 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 June 20 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 June 21 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 July 18 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 August 16 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 September 20 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 October 22 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 November 21 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1957 December 18 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1958 January 23 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1958 April 22 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1958 May 21 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1958 June 5 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. D-1-G, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1956 October 31 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1956 November 19 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 January 2 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 February 20 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 March 13 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 April 9 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 April 30 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 June 19 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 July 5 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 August 6 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 September 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 October 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 November 4 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 December 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 January 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 February 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 March 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 May 8 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 May 27 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1956 October-1957 June (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1957 July-December (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. D-2-G, 1958 January-May (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 August 16 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 September 17 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 October 1, 3, & 18 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 November 17 & 19 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 December 20 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 January 21 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 February 20 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 March 18 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 March 31 & April 18 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 May 25 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 June 21 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 July 18 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 August 16 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 September 20 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 November 20 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 December 18 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 January 23 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 March 4 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 April 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 April 22 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 May 21 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 June 19 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1956 August-December (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1957 January-November (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. E-1-G, 1958 January-June (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 March 29 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 May 24 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 July 24 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 August 23 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 November 22 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 December 23 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 January 28 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 February 25 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 March 28 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 April 25 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 May 26 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 June 24 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1957 March-December (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. F-1-G, 1958 January-June (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 May 14-15 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 July 15 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 August 12 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 September 12 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 October 15 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 November 12 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 December 13 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 January 23 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 March 17 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 April 17 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 May 13 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 June 12 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 July 10 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 August 8 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 September 5 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1957 May-December (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 January-June (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. F-2-G, 1958 July-September (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 September 27 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Virginia Engineering Co., Inc., contractors
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 October 22 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 October 23 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 November 25 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 December 23 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1958 January 25 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1958 February 22 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1958 March 22 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1957 October-December (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. P-10-TA, 1958 January-March (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1957 October 25 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    J. Kennon Perrin Co., contractors
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1957 November 29 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1957 December 27 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1958 January 29 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1958 February 28 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1958 March 28 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1958 April 24 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1958 May 26 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. P-12-ADM, 1957 October-1958 July (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1957 December 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Walden & Flournoy, Inc., contractors
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1957 December 27 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 January 29 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 February 28 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 March 28 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 April 24 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 May 26 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 June 16 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 July 28 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1957 December-1958 April (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Contract No. P-13-MB, 1958 May-July (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Oversize photographs [note box number], ca. 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)